{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1bbbed0dadcccc431c9c"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-important-soft-skills-to-have?-", 
    "answer" : "It might be your hard skills that get you the interview, but it’s the soft skills that bring you success in your career. Soft skills are your personal capabilities that determine how well you work with others, job performance, communication and all of the other things that make you different from every other expert in your field. While your technical expertise is very important, soft skills are much harder to teach. These can be a deciding factor in getting and keeping your dream job. In this post, we’ll outline nine soft skills that will make you successful in your career or in the classroom, and some tips to help you develop them further. Interpersonal communication is the backbone of all soft skills. Whether it’s through emails, phone calls or in person, you need to be a clear communicat Continue Reading It might be your hard skills that get you the interview, but it’s the soft skills that bring you success in your career. Soft skills are your personal capabilities that determine how well you work with others, job performance, communication and all of the other things that make you different from every other expert in your field. While your technical expertise is very important, soft skills are much harder to teach. These can be a deciding factor in getting and keeping your dream job. In this post, we’ll outline nine soft skills that will make you successful in your career or in the classroom, and some tips to help you develop them further. Interpersonal communication is the backbone of all soft skills. Whether it’s through emails, phone calls or in person, you need to be a clear communicat Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:48:11.506+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the most important soft skills to have? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1bd1ed0dadcccc431cab"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-soft-skills-everyone-should-try-to-develop?-Why?-When-and-how-can-they-be-applied?-", 
    "answer" : "Nela Canovic, 10,000 hours and counting on becoming the best version of myself.Answered 4 years ago · Featured on news.com.au · Author has 1.1K answers and 29.2M answer viewsWhat are some soft skills everyone should try to develop? Why? When and how can they be applied? Nela Canovic Here are 10 soft skills you should focus on, why they’re important to you, and how to practice them daily.  ONE. Practice gratitude. Why? It trains your brain to focus on positive things and makes you think of what you already have in your life as opposed to what you do not.It keeps you grounded in your personal life so you are less focused on what others are doing with theirs, which is a huge waste of time and won’t help you get any closer to your personal goals.How to practice it? Each morning, take 5 minutes to write down or say aloud 3 things you are grateful for having in your life right now. It can be something as simple as having a roof over your head, a warm bed to sleep in, food in your fridge, clean running water and electricity, or a great relationship with a family member, a partnerContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:48:33.900+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are some soft skills everyone should try to develop? Why? When and how can they be applied? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1c23ed0dadcccc431cde"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-improve-my-communication-skill-and-as-well-as-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Vipul SrivastaVa Skills that corresponds to technical knowledge are often imbibed during the course that you generally open but what about soft skills. We never learn them on daily basis but develop as per own understanding. The companies are gaining pace and to sustain that speed they are in search of those soft skills. In order to be successful in coming years it is better to hone those skills which can be done via Soft Skill training in Delhi NCR provided by Heal and Rise foundation and brush up the dust and gradually grow into the one that is in demand in the employment of present time. Yet we are aware of this truth but we overlook it.  Do not worry as Heal and Rise safeguards your interest as : · The best soft skill training is provided by the members of the foundation as they give priority to individua Continue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:49:55.963+0000"), 
    "question" : "How can I improve my communication skill and as well as soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1c46ed0dadcccc431ceb"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-best-way-to-improve-soft-skills-effectively?-", 
    "answer" : "To get your foot in the door at your dream job, it’s important to have solid credentials: a degree, work experience, and professional references. But it’s your soft skills—not hard-hitting credentials and technical know-how—that ultimately determine your employability and staying power. Soft skills help you work more effectively in your chosen career, build solid professional relationships, and navigate challenges that arise on the job. Strayer online degrees include courses that help you develop these skills, so you’re ready to thrive in any work environment. 10 ESSENTIAL SOFT SKILLS: CommunicationA good communicator is able to articulate their ideas and genuinely listen to other people. Communication skills include writing, speaking, active listening, and http://collaboration.At work, you nContinue Reading To get your foot in the door at your dream job, it’s important to have solid credentials: a degree, work experience, and professional references. But it’s your soft skills—not hard-hitting credentials and technical know-how—that ultimately determine your employability and staying power. Soft skills help you work more effectively in your chosen career, build solid professional relationships, and navigate challenges that arise on the job. Strayer online degrees include courses that help you develop these skills, so you’re ready to thrive in any work environment. 10 ESSENTIAL SOFT SKILLS: CommunicationA good communicator is able to articulate their ideas and genuinely listen to other people. Communication skills include writing, speaking, active listening, and http://collaboration.At work, you nContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:50:30.572+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is best way to improve soft skills effectively? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1c88ed0dadcccc431d1a"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-important-are-soft-skills-in-today’s-world?-", 
    "answer" : "Need of Soft Skills in Students: In this era of tough competition in corporate world, companies do not hire candidates with high percentage, they hire professionals with great people skills. It is important for every college student to work on their speaking skills, reasoning ability, thinking skills and emotional quotient to grow in the corporate. But are students serious about these traits? Are they working on their skills while studying in college? Isn’t it sad that most of the students think about improving their skills after completing their study. But right time to improve these skills are while in college. Let’s explore what are these skills and why it is important? Soft Skills: Soft skills are personality traits and behaviors. Unlike technical or ‘hard’ skills, soft skills are not about th Continue Reading Need of Soft Skills in Students: In this era of tough competition in corporate world, companies do not hire candidates with high percentage, they hire professionals with great people skills. It is important for every college student to work on their speaking skills, reasoning ability, thinking skills and emotional quotient to grow in the corporate. But are students serious about these traits? Are they working on their skills while studying in college? Isn’t it sad that most of the students think about improving their skills after completing their study. But right time to improve these skills are while in college. Let’s explore what are these skills and why it is important? Soft Skills: Soft skills are personality traits and behaviors. Unlike technical or ‘hard’ skills, soft skills are not about th Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:51:36.642+0000"), 
    "question" : "How important are soft skills in today’s world? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1caced0dadcccc431d2b"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-needed-to-become-a-soft-skills-trainer?-", 
    "answer" : "Subject matter knowledge and training skills are both needed for one to become a trainer in any field. In addition, one must have a passion for training. ICBI is amongst the leading brands in the world, and a pioneer in the Indian sub-continent, in training and certifying people to become Image Consultants and Soft Skills trainers. In its near decade of presence, with footprint across 14 cities and its recently introduced online live programs, ICBI has become the most credible choice for those wanting to get associated with a profession in the people transformation space. An alumni base of near 5000 live-wire Image Consultants and Trainers work closely with individuals, corporates, academic institutions and NGOs, enabling people to build themselves for competitive advantage and subsequent  Continue Reading Subject matter knowledge and training skills are both needed for one to become a trainer in any field. In addition, one must have a passion for training. ICBI is amongst the leading brands in the world, and a pioneer in the Indian sub-continent, in training and certifying people to become Image Consultants and Soft Skills trainers. In its near decade of presence, with footprint across 14 cities and its recently introduced online live programs, ICBI has become the most credible choice for those wanting to get associated with a profession in the people transformation space. An alumni base of near 5000 live-wire Image Consultants and Trainers work closely with individuals, corporates, academic institutions and NGOs, enabling people to build themselves for competitive advantage and subsequent  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:52:12.975+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are needed to become a soft skills trainer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1ceced0dadcccc431d4c"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-meant-by-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Saurabh Sharma Soft Skills, strictly going by the definition, means intangible and immeasurable skills. That’s difficult to digest, right? So, read on to know how simple yet extremely significant Soft Skills are in our life. Skills are acquired. They’re a result of a lot of hardwork and skills represent your expertise in something which you can do deftly after a considerable time of practise. So, there are two broad categories in Skills: Hard Skills and Soft Skills. Let’s understand each one of them by learning the differences between the two. Hard Skills are the ones which represents the core study or specific area which is called - concentration or major in various parts of the world. It represents and demonstrates your mastery in a particular field. It can be measured - regular tests are taken by you in  Continue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:53:16.145+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is meant by soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1d0bed0dadcccc431d63"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-top-soft-skill-a-potential-employer-looks-for-in-a-candidate?-", 
    "answer" : "Gone are the days when one just had to simply show off his resume to land a job. Today, the interviewer asks, what else? No piece of paper can save you from that question. In that moment, if you manage to convey your message in an effective manner, you’re in, otherwise, you’re out. Creative and effective communication is a soft skill among others that differentiates you from the masses. In order to nail a job of your dreams and work at a respectable position, you need great soft skills such as : Positive Attitude - A positive attitude can do wonders in turning a department or company around. Having employees who possess a positive attitude can also be contagious; and for employers, it’s important for them to seek that kind of energy since it only takes a few negative people to bring down a dContinue Reading Gone are the days when one just had to simply show off his resume to land a job. Today, the interviewer asks, what else? No piece of paper can save you from that question. In that moment, if you manage to convey your message in an effective manner, you’re in, otherwise, you’re out. Creative and effective communication is a soft skill among others that differentiates you from the masses. In order to nail a job of your dreams and work at a respectable position, you need great soft skills such as : Positive Attitude - A positive attitude can do wonders in turning a department or company around. Having employees who possess a positive attitude can also be contagious; and for employers, it’s important for them to seek that kind of energy since it only takes a few negative people to bring down a dContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:53:47.656+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is the top soft skill a potential employer looks for in a candidate? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1d2aed0dadcccc431d71"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-certifications-to-become-a-corporate-trainer-in-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Hi there, A corporate trainer in soft skills helps to improve communication skills and relevant facts to train the employee. Soft skills may not help an apprentice perform a specific master job-related topic. They are an invaluable part of the learning process. In training, it builds soft skills courses for corporate learning needed in the modern workplace. Skills effectively manage their time, increase their productivity, and become an integral part of a team. Soft skills incorporate people's abilities, social, character, interpersonal, and portable. Hard skills are technical skills for job-specific criteria. The hard skills come from education, certifications, training, and work experience. Hard skills involve the particular information and expertise required for the achievement of a job. h Continue Reading Hi there, A corporate trainer in soft skills helps to improve communication skills and relevant facts to train the employee. Soft skills may not help an apprentice perform a specific master job-related topic. They are an invaluable part of the learning process. In training, it builds soft skills courses for corporate learning needed in the modern workplace. Skills effectively manage their time, increase their productivity, and become an integral part of a team. Soft skills incorporate people's abilities, social, character, interpersonal, and portable. Hard skills are technical skills for job-specific criteria. The hard skills come from education, certifications, training, and work experience. Hard skills involve the particular information and expertise required for the achievement of a job. h Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:54:18.717+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the certifications to become a corporate trainer in soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1db8ed0dadcccc431dc1"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-soft-skills-are-basic-in-working?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What soft skills are basic in working?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:56:40.982+0000"), 
    "question" : "What soft skills are basic in working? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1dd7ed0dadcccc431dd3"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-improve-my-soft-skills-in-speaking?-", 
    "answer" : "To improve in speaking, practice speaking with the intent to improve. Define what it is that you wish to improve upon in speaking. The more detail you are the easier it is for you to know what needs to be done in order for you to improve. In seeking to improve in “speaking” as a general and all-inclusive term may seem on paper to make things easier. With so many aspects of “Speaking” there must be something that will fit the needs, wants, learning style and time. Yet in practice the opposite is true. And here is Buridan’s Ass to shed light on why that is. So get as detail as you can and then practice doing it with focus and the intention of getting better. Be aware of what’s going on. why it is you are getting the desired or undesired results that you are getting. The more you practice and  Continue Reading To improve in speaking, practice speaking with the intent to improve. Define what it is that you wish to improve upon in speaking. The more detail you are the easier it is for you to know what needs to be done in order for you to improve. In seeking to improve in “speaking” as a general and all-inclusive term may seem on paper to make things easier. With so many aspects of “Speaking” there must be something that will fit the needs, wants, learning style and time. Yet in practice the opposite is true. And here is Buridan’s Ass to shed light on why that is. So get as detail as you can and then practice doing it with focus and the intention of getting better. Be aware of what’s going on. why it is you are getting the desired or undesired results that you are getting. The more you practice and  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:57:11.526+0000"), 
    "question" : "How can I improve my soft skills in speaking? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1e26ed0dadcccc431e0c"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-books-for-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "I could recommend my own Book titled “Sizzling Soft Skills For Spectacular Success”.(ISBN9781947137332), recently published , as the most resourceful and helpful book on the Topic of Soft Skills. This book deals with 10 of the most powerful Soft Skills, like 1. Effective Communication Skills 2. Interpersonal Skills 3. Art of Learning 4. Analytical Ability 5. Positive Thinking 6. Time Management 7. Goal Setting 8. Innovation & Creativity 9. Personal Hygiene and Personal Grooming, and 10. Enthusiasm. In this Book, I have given clear description of the various connotations of these Soft Skills , with numerous real life examples, most of them drawn from my own Student Population, giving systematic instructions on how to develop these Soft Skills by self study and practice. The Book has already received man Continue Reading I could recommend my own Book titled “Sizzling Soft Skills For Spectacular Success”.(ISBN9781947137332), recently published , as the most resourceful and helpful book on the Topic of Soft Skills. This book deals with 10 of the most powerful Soft Skills, like 1. Effective Communication Skills 2. Interpersonal Skills 3. Art of Learning 4. Analytical Ability 5. Positive Thinking 6. Time Management 7. Goal Setting 8. Innovation & Creativity 9. Personal Hygiene and Personal Grooming, and 10. Enthusiasm. In this Book, I have given clear description of the various connotations of these Soft Skills , with numerous real life examples, most of them drawn from my own Student Population, giving systematic instructions on how to develop these Soft Skills by self study and practice. The Book has already received man Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:58:30.321+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the best books for soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1e2eed0dadcccc431e1f"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-soft-skills-that-will-make-you-success-at-work?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the soft skills that will make you success at work?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:58:38.517+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the soft skills that will make you success at work? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1e67ed0dadcccc431e31"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-soft-skills-trainings-worth-it?-", 
    "answer" : "A clear change is seen in the workplace from the last ten years. The way of job requirements and hiring potential managers have also changed with this. As the “hard skills” such as technical knowledge and education are still important that can’t be ignored but presently “Soft Skills” complement hard skills. The workplaces are trying to improve soft skills that are not making from their human resources. What Do the Soft Skills Entail? Soft skills have many forms and it can be defined as a combination of people and social skills most importantly communication. This also includes one’s personal attitudes toward workplace ambience. Though this can be included these below-mentioned traits but are not limited to these such - Effective communication skillsThe ability to cope up under pressureEmpathyContinue Reading A clear change is seen in the workplace from the last ten years. The way of job requirements and hiring potential managers have also changed with this. As the “hard skills” such as technical knowledge and education are still important that can’t be ignored but presently “Soft Skills” complement hard skills. The workplaces are trying to improve soft skills that are not making from their human resources. What Do the Soft Skills Entail? Soft skills have many forms and it can be defined as a combination of people and social skills most importantly communication. This also includes one’s personal attitudes toward workplace ambience. Though this can be included these below-mentioned traits but are not limited to these such - Effective communication skillsThe ability to cope up under pressureEmpathyContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T07:59:35.602+0000"), 
    "question" : "Are soft skills trainings worth it? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1e8fed0dadcccc431e4a"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-soft-skills-are-important-for-Chartered-Accountants?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Sai Sirish", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:00:15.330+0000"), 
    "question" : "Which soft skills are important for Chartered Accountants? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1ebded0dadcccc431e67"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-hard-skills-and-soft-skills-I-should-develop-in-myself?-", 
    "answer" : "Shubham Sudrania Here they are, 1. How Can You Compete in Today's Workplace?  Whoever said, \"it's a rat race out there\" knew nothing about how competitive today's workplace would be. Rats have it easy! Make it through a maze, grab your treat and you're done. It's not enough to be the best at what you do. Having the hard skills you need to excel at your occupation is a requirement, but being the best at your job won't help you win the race. Having competitive skills employers value will. Let's take a look at what they are. 2. Stop Talking and Start Listening  Some people think they can talk their way to the top. Sharing your knowledge with others is certainly important, but listening can benefit you in so many ways. You can learn a lot when you make an effort to understand what others are saying to you. As an act Continue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:01:01.218+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the hard skills and soft skills I should develop in myself? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1ed7ed0dadcccc431e70"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-your-single-best-advice-for-improving-soft-skills-in-the-workplace?-", 
    "answer" : "Instead of giving you a single piece of advice, let me give you a curation of the single best advice for soft skills improvement from different people: Aiyswarya Kamate ‘s single best advice for you is GET OUT OF YOUR COMFORT ZONE. She thinks, The more you practice putting yourself out there, the better you will communicate . I agree. Getting out of the comfort zone is essential for development of soft skills. But, many people beginning the journey of soft-skills improvement find it very difficult to do so. May be doing it together with something fun would help. At SBB, We are trying to do that by using performing arts as a medium for soft-skills improvement. It gives people an easy platform to get out of their comfort zone and still be comfortable. Mike Schoultz wants you to try new things  Continue Reading Instead of giving you a single piece of advice, let me give you a curation of the single best advice for soft skills improvement from different people: Aiyswarya Kamate ‘s single best advice for you is GET OUT OF YOUR COMFORT ZONE. She thinks, The more you practice putting yourself out there, the better you will communicate . I agree. Getting out of the comfort zone is essential for development of soft skills. But, many people beginning the journey of soft-skills improvement find it very difficult to do so. May be doing it together with something fun would help. At SBB, We are trying to do that by using performing arts as a medium for soft-skills improvement. It gives people an easy platform to get out of their comfort zone and still be comfortable. Mike Schoultz wants you to try new things  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:01:27.349+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is your single best advice for improving soft skills in the workplace? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1ef1ed0dadcccc431e86"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-soft-skills-compulsory-when-you-have-the-required-technical-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "You will appreciate the value and the relative significance of Soft Skills better if you understand the relationship between Hard Skills and Soft Skills more clearly. This analogy will help you for better understanding. Hard Skills are like the Hardware of a computer whereas the Soft Skills can be compared to a Software. As you know, the Hardware is an essential part of the computer without which the computer cannot work at all. However, imagine what would be the real value and usefulness of even a costly computer if it is not combined with the suitable and necessary software. Will it be able to deliver the results ? Simply, no ! The same is the case here. Suppose a candidate has extraordinary technical skills in many computer-related activities but unfortunately, he does not possess important  Continue Reading You will appreciate the value and the relative significance of Soft Skills better if you understand the relationship between Hard Skills and Soft Skills more clearly. This analogy will help you for better understanding. Hard Skills are like the Hardware of a computer whereas the Soft Skills can be compared to a Software. As you know, the Hardware is an essential part of the computer without which the computer cannot work at all. However, imagine what would be the real value and usefulness of even a costly computer if it is not combined with the suitable and necessary software. Will it be able to deliver the results ? Simply, no ! The same is the case here. Suppose a candidate has extraordinary technical skills in many computer-related activities but unfortunately, he does not possess important  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:01:53.894+0000"), 
    "question" : "Why are soft skills compulsory when you have the required technical skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1f0eed0dadcccc431e97"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-soft-skills-are-crucial-to-data-scientists?-", 
    "answer" : "Vijay Sathish Communicating at the level of your audience Scenario 1 - Recently, I was in a foreign country for a quarterly business review meeting with a big banking partner representing my company. (how big, you might ask - among the top 25 banks in the world by size of operation, since you asked) Now, what would a data scientist have to do at a business meeting, you might ask? Now, I was there to answer questions related to risk (machine learning) models that we had developed for the bank to underwrite small business loans for them. There were about 25 people in the meeting room. All 15 from the bank were business people - heads of business development, risk, marketing and some project and program managers. From the Kabbage team, only two of us were technical, and the other represented software enginee Continue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:02:22.876+0000"), 
    "question" : "What soft skills are crucial to data scientists? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1f25ed0dadcccc431eac"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-soft-skills-and-how-to-develop-them?-", 
    "answer" : "What is soft skills? A set of skills that helps you do well in inter-personal communication. The main components of communication would be speaking, writing, reading and listening. Soft skills include qualities like being able to customise your communication and body language, assertive skills, negotiations, stress management, time management etc. If you ask me, working on your communication skills alone can make your soft skills better. A few ways to do that would be: 1. Reading: Read something every single day. And I don’t mean just newspapers. Read books – from fiction to non-fiction. (Skip Chetan Bhagat and his recent followers please) There is so much in the writing of great authors that can boost ones knowledge and thinking. Online articles on different topics can also aid the process Continue Reading What is soft skills? A set of skills that helps you do well in inter-personal communication. The main components of communication would be speaking, writing, reading and listening. Soft skills include qualities like being able to customise your communication and body language, assertive skills, negotiations, stress management, time management etc. If you ask me, working on your communication skills alone can make your soft skills better. A few ways to do that would be: 1. Reading: Read something every single day. And I don’t mean just newspapers. Read books – from fiction to non-fiction. (Skip Chetan Bhagat and his recent followers please) There is so much in the writing of great authors that can boost ones knowledge and thinking. Online articles on different topics can also aid the process Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:02:45.914+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are soft skills and how to develop them? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1f4ced0dadcccc431eb9"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-a-soft-skills-trainer-in-India?-", 
    "answer" : "Ameer Ali, Language Expert,SoftSkills Book Author, Empowerment Trainer.Answered 3 years ago · Author has 1K answers and 2.1M answer viewsHow do I become a soft skills trainer in India? Ameer Ali", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:03:24.343+0000"), 
    "question" : "How do I become a soft skills trainer in India? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1f6eed0dadcccc431ed2"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-soft-skills-that-engineering-graduates-should-have?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some soft skills that engineering graduates should have?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:03:58.327+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are some soft skills that engineering graduates should have? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1f86ed0dadcccc431edb"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-institute-for-soft-skill-development-in-India?-", 
    "answer" : "Hi! Trust all well! I always admire people who take up the challenge to become a Life-coach or a motivational speaker, student for personality development, acquiring interview and GD skills or else, a soft skills and corporate trainer. Well, i am known for few-liners so, without taking much time i would say that if you were looking for a government cerification then go for ISTD and many other platforms. Experience is enough to make audience motivated however, they would only come to you after learning about your certifications and achievements. Even, you will get entry into clients’ plsace due to certifications only. People who want to take time and get lot of exposure(**like visiting schools colleges and corporate along with me as co-trainer, guest speaker and for motivational speech**), the Continue Reading Hi! Trust all well! I always admire people who take up the challenge to become a Life-coach or a motivational speaker, student for personality development, acquiring interview and GD skills or else, a soft skills and corporate trainer. Well, i am known for few-liners so, without taking much time i would say that if you were looking for a government cerification then go for ISTD and many other platforms. Experience is enough to make audience motivated however, they would only come to you after learning about your certifications and achievements. Even, you will get entry into clients’ plsace due to certifications only. People who want to take time and get lot of exposure(**like visiting schools colleges and corporate along with me as co-trainer, guest speaker and for motivational speech**), the Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:04:22.962+0000"), 
    "question" : "Which is the best institute for soft skill development in India? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1fcaed0dadcccc431efd"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-important-are-soft-skills-for-a-consultant?-", 
    "answer" : "A2A. If you have good soft skills, it can carry you a long way in consulting. No doubt. But the question asks how important are soft skills, and the subquestion details specifically asks about whether one needs stellar presentation skills for consulting. While anecdotal, I wanted to look at some disconfirming evidence from my past. Honestly, my views might be a bit controversial. I have seen the following types of successful consultants: Those who have despicable traits as human beings. Senior people who junior people hate and where clients have wanted the senior person replaced.Those I would not want to hang out with because they lack friendly, interpersonal skills, but who are totally professional.Those who create mediocre presentations from the perspective of either being loaded with moundContinue Reading A2A. If you have good soft skills, it can carry you a long way in consulting. No doubt. But the question asks how important are soft skills, and the subquestion details specifically asks about whether one needs stellar presentation skills for consulting. While anecdotal, I wanted to look at some disconfirming evidence from my past. Honestly, my views might be a bit controversial. I have seen the following types of successful consultants: Those who have despicable traits as human beings. Senior people who junior people hate and where clients have wanted the senior person replaced.Those I would not want to hang out with because they lack friendly, interpersonal skills, but who are totally professional.Those who create mediocre presentations from the perspective of either being loaded with moundContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:05:30.272+0000"), 
    "question" : "How important are soft skills for a consultant? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1fdfed0dadcccc431f13"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-improve-my-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "1.Develop communication skills.2.Practice active listening skills.3.Build relationships.4.Practice leading.5.Take initiative.for more info about these five points please click on the link below How to Improve Soft Skills", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:05:51.823+0000"), 
    "question" : "How do I improve my soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e1ff7ed0dadcccc431f1c"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-important-are-soft-skills-in-helping-people-achieve-success-in-their-job-or-career?-", 
    "answer" : "Most people who succeed are not the ones who are the best at their jobs, but the ones who remain consistent and know how to deal with the people at their jobs. Do you often find yourself complaining about that co-worker who works the fewest hours and is still the boss's favorite? While you may excel at your job, that person excels at something more important: Dealing with the boss.  Indian workplaces have always antagonized people with great soft skills and called them \"encomiasts\" or “bootlickers”. While some people unarguably may be so, other may just have better soft skills. However unfair it may sound, unless you are uncharacteristically amazing at your job, you need people to like you. When people like your work, they'll gradually like you. But when people like you, you get chances to s Continue Reading Most people who succeed are not the ones who are the best at their jobs, but the ones who remain consistent and know how to deal with the people at their jobs. Do you often find yourself complaining about that co-worker who works the fewest hours and is still the boss's favorite? While you may excel at your job, that person excels at something more important: Dealing with the boss.  Indian workplaces have always antagonized people with great soft skills and called them \"encomiasts\" or “bootlickers”. While some people unarguably may be so, other may just have better soft skills. However unfair it may sound, unless you are uncharacteristically amazing at your job, you need people to like you. When people like your work, they'll gradually like you. But when people like you, you get chances to s Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:06:15.263+0000"), 
    "question" : "How important are soft skills in helping people achieve success in their job or career? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2015ed0dadcccc431f33"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-develop-my-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Bonam Venkata Nagarjuna", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:06:45.775+0000"), 
    "question" : "How do I develop my soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e202eed0dadcccc431f41"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-certification-necessary-for-soft-skill-trainers?-", 
    "answer" : "Mayank Gupta, Soft Skills Trainer (2013-present)Answered 1 year ago · Author has 74 answers and 1.9M answer viewsIs certification necessary for soft skill trainers? Mayank Gupta What is a certificate?  Image is just for the reference purpose. (Image courtesy_google) According to the National Council on Measurement in Education, a certification test is a credentialing test used to determine whether individuals are knowledgeable enough in a given occupational area to be labeled \"competent to practice\" in that area. In simple words, when someone else decides that you are competent enough or not! It’s very important in very technical domains like Medical, IT and Engineering because there is only one right way. So either you are right or wrong. And if you are wrong the consequences will be severe. But in training it doesn’t work the same way. Sometimes the best trainers are not even certified. Sometimes the certified trainers are the best. In training certified = doesn’t mat Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:07:10.566+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is certification necessary for soft skill trainers? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2076ed0dadcccc431f64"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-soft-skills-to-learn-online?-", 
    "answer" : "Jai Kumar, BBA from Delhi Technological University (2021)Answered 8 months ago · Author has 82 answers and 21.6K answer viewsWhich are the soft skills to learn online? Jai Kumar Soft skills are personal attributes, personality traits, inherent social cues, and communication abilities needed for success on the job. Soft skills characterize how a person interacts in his or her relationships with others.  Yes, there are several institutes that provide soft skills courses online. you will get the details mentioned below. Edu4sureCourserayoutubeudemythere are courses which are paid as well as free of cost. Like youtube which is free anyone can go and learn about the any topic. but the disadvantage is nobody will give attention over there. you only gain knowledge for that topic. Other than that Edu4sure, Coursera and udemy are the online platforms that provide several courses on their website. I suggest Edu4sure because of these points given below. updated curriculumExperieContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:08:22.881+0000"), 
    "question" : "Which are the soft skills to learn online? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e208aed0dadcccc431f78"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-soft-skills-help-make-a-good-doctor?-", 
    "answer" : "Good Communication Skills This is the most important skill that a doctor can posses, especially in this day and age when the doctor-patient relationship is at stake. A way of speaking openly and transparently along with the ability to distill complex treatment procedures into simple words to ensure that the patient and his family can give informed consent goes a long way in making the patient feel secure about their condition and their decisions. Time Management Abilities In a country, where practicing medicine is always a battle against time, it is important to treat time as a very valuable resource. As I have already talked about in an answer before, seeing more patients in a day even at the cost of consultation time makes sense in a government setting (but not in a private setting!). Knowin Continue Reading Good Communication Skills This is the most important skill that a doctor can posses, especially in this day and age when the doctor-patient relationship is at stake. A way of speaking openly and transparently along with the ability to distill complex treatment procedures into simple words to ensure that the patient and his family can give informed consent goes a long way in making the patient feel secure about their condition and their decisions. Time Management Abilities In a country, where practicing medicine is always a battle against time, it is important to treat time as a very valuable resource. As I have already talked about in an answer before, seeing more patients in a day even at the cost of consultation time makes sense in a government setting (but not in a private setting!). Knowin Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:08:42.415+0000"), 
    "question" : "What soft skills help make a good doctor? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e209fed0dadcccc431f80"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-companies-really-value-soft-skills-over-hard-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Yes, companies value Soft Skills more than Hard Skills ( this may be a ‘hard pill’ for many to swallow, but it is the harsh fact glaring at all of us today !), for the following reasons: Hard Skills are academic or technical skills, and almost every candidate today possesses one of these skills or the other. Otherwise, he or she won’t even be called for the Interview. So the Hard Skills can take you upto the Interview Room. What happens there ?Soft Skills are the other important category of skills which actually equip and enable the candidate to properly utilise his Hard Skills at the workplace. Some of these important Soft Skills are Creative Communication Skills, Team Spirit, Problem Solving Skills, Quick Learning Ability, Positive Thinking, etc. Without these skills, a candidate’s usefulContinue Reading Yes, companies value Soft Skills more than Hard Skills ( this may be a ‘hard pill’ for many to swallow, but it is the harsh fact glaring at all of us today !), for the following reasons: Hard Skills are academic or technical skills, and almost every candidate today possesses one of these skills or the other. Otherwise, he or she won’t even be called for the Interview. So the Hard Skills can take you upto the Interview Room. What happens there ?Soft Skills are the other important category of skills which actually equip and enable the candidate to properly utilise his Hard Skills at the workplace. Some of these important Soft Skills are Creative Communication Skills, Team Spirit, Problem Solving Skills, Quick Learning Ability, Positive Thinking, etc. Without these skills, a candidate’s usefulContinue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:09:03.592+0000"), 
    "question" : "Do companies really value soft skills over hard skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e20b4ed0dadcccc431f88"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-soft-skills-must-learned-in-college?-", 
    "answer" : "Madison Wang It's great you are thinking of advancing your soft skills while you are still in college. Team assignments and club activities are the best and most accessible ways you can learn and practice your soft skills while in college. Team assignments: you know how a lot of students dread team assignments? Based on what I remembered from my own college days, plus stories I heard from our college interns, the most challenging part is to get your teammates to do their part of the work, and occasionally resolve conflicts among teammates. So next time you have to work in a team, volunteer to be the team lead, and see what you can do to make sure your fellow teammates do their work on time, without resenting you or each other. A few suggestions come to mind: Make sure everyone is clear what they need to woContinue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:09:24.758+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the soft skills must learned in college? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e20d4ed0dadcccc431fa0"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-a-career-as-a-soft-skill-trainer?-", 
    "answer" : "There is a lot of scope depending on the area of training you choose. Soft Skills a vast area and it is not a good idea to try and train everyone on everything. So one of the first things you should do is to figure out the niche you want to be an expert in. Build your personal brand accordingly. SKILLS REQUIRED AS A CORPORATE TRAINER Confidence: I don’t just mean confidence that you can train but also facing people and talking to them. You should preferably be an extrovert and like meeting people and working with people. Confidence is also being able to talk well and be able to hold people’s attention while you do that. If facing people gives you the jitters, this isn’t the right career for you. Communication skills: This term itself is pregnant with meaning. It goes without saying that your  Continue Reading There is a lot of scope depending on the area of training you choose. Soft Skills a vast area and it is not a good idea to try and train everyone on everything. So one of the first things you should do is to figure out the niche you want to be an expert in. Build your personal brand accordingly. SKILLS REQUIRED AS A CORPORATE TRAINER Confidence: I don’t just mean confidence that you can train but also facing people and talking to them. You should preferably be an extrovert and like meeting people and working with people. Confidence is also being able to talk well and be able to hold people’s attention while you do that. If facing people gives you the jitters, this isn’t the right career for you. Communication skills: This term itself is pregnant with meaning. It goes without saying that your  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:09:56.246+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is the scope of a career as a soft skill trainer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e20ebed0dadcccc431faa"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-good-institutes-for-soft-skills-training?-", 
    "answer" : "ICBI is amongst the leading brands in the world, and a pioneer in the Indian sub-continent, in training and certifying people to become Image Consultants and Soft Skills trainers. In its near decade of presence, with footprint across 14 cities and its recently introduced online live programs, ICBI has become the most credible choice for those wanting to get associated with a profession in the people transformation space. An alumni base of near 5000 live-wire Image Consultants and Trainers work closely with individuals, corporates, academic institutions and NGOs, enabling people to build themselves for competitive advantage and subsequent success. ICBI has curriculum alliances, and certification accreditations with top national and international institutions. Over 1000 corporates and Institu Continue Reading ICBI is amongst the leading brands in the world, and a pioneer in the Indian sub-continent, in training and certifying people to become Image Consultants and Soft Skills trainers. In its near decade of presence, with footprint across 14 cities and its recently introduced online live programs, ICBI has become the most credible choice for those wanting to get associated with a profession in the people transformation space. An alumni base of near 5000 live-wire Image Consultants and Trainers work closely with individuals, corporates, academic institutions and NGOs, enabling people to build themselves for competitive advantage and subsequent success. ICBI has curriculum alliances, and certification accreditations with top national and international institutions. Over 1000 corporates and Institu Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:10:19.656+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are good institutes for soft skills training? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2101ed0dadcccc431fc0"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-and-how-can-one-buy-exercises-for-soft-skills-training?-", 
    "answer" : "Dale Emery  Actually the fact that you have identified some areas for soft skill training is already a great progress in you .the next thing which you should be doing to be assimilating the inspiring voices of achievers who  have turned around impossible things in their life themselves . It will get you into a positive momentum and inspiration and probably you will find the right way to manage people- through their consciousness....(Your mental knowledge can compliment but your state of consciousness will definitely make you do the right things )", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:10:41.032+0000"), 
    "question" : "Where and how can one buy exercises for soft-skills training? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2164ed0dadcccc431ff3"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-future-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:12:20.678+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the future soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2184ed0dadcccc43200a"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-important-soft-skills-which-can-be-used-in-daily-life?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the most important soft skills to have?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:12:52.121+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the important soft skills which can be used in daily life? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e219eed0dadcccc432014"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-ways-to-improve-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some good ways to improve soft skills?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:13:18.934+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are some good ways to improve soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e21c8ed0dadcccc43202e"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-enhance-my-communication-and-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Soft skills is a pretty large area, covering from Communication Skills, Listening Skills, Leadership Skills, Motivating Skills, Negotiation Skills… just to name a few. If you try to do too many things at the same time, you won’t succeed at anything. So it may be better to focus on 1 or 2 of these skills which you think you are weak at, or would like to improve further. One of the biggest skill that you must master is to be good at Communications… with your peers, your subordinates, your bosses, vendors, friends, pretty much every one. Communication goes much deeper than simply speaking… although speaking alone is not easy. To communicate effectively and efficiently, you must be able to talk and listen attentively. Then put across your points concisely. Many people only want to talk, and keep  Continue Reading Soft skills is a pretty large area, covering from Communication Skills, Listening Skills, Leadership Skills, Motivating Skills, Negotiation Skills… just to name a few. If you try to do too many things at the same time, you won’t succeed at anything. So it may be better to focus on 1 or 2 of these skills which you think you are weak at, or would like to improve further. One of the biggest skill that you must master is to be good at Communications… with your peers, your subordinates, your bosses, vendors, friends, pretty much every one. Communication goes much deeper than simply speaking… although speaking alone is not easy. To communicate effectively and efficiently, you must be able to talk and listen attentively. Then put across your points concisely. Many people only want to talk, and keep  Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:14:00.503+0000"), 
    "question" : "How do I enhance my communication and soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e21dced0dadcccc432036"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-soft-skills-of-civil-engineer?-", 
    "answer" : "Report writing is by far the top soft skill for an engineer. An engineer who is also a good writer can work on multiple tasks and across disciplines and has far better chances to progress in their career than a less soft skilled engineer. He or she can move from technical tasks to project management and business development roles. I give you a personal example. When I started as structural engineer, I struggled to put together a few sentences and write the reports I was asked to produce by my manager. He was an excellent writer and good communicator who from a technical role moved up the ladder to be a company director. I badly wanted to be like him but it wasn't until I migrated to Australia and became a manager that my writing skills took off. For me there was also the language barrier as E Continue Reading Report writing is by far the top soft skill for an engineer. An engineer who is also a good writer can work on multiple tasks and across disciplines and has far better chances to progress in their career than a less soft skilled engineer. He or she can move from technical tasks to project management and business development roles. I give you a personal example. When I started as structural engineer, I struggled to put together a few sentences and write the reports I was asked to produce by my manager. He was an excellent writer and good communicator who from a technical role moved up the ladder to be a company director. I badly wanted to be like him but it wasn't until I migrated to Australia and became a manager that my writing skills took off. For me there was also the language barrier as E Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:14:20.550+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are soft skills of civil engineer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e21f3ed0dadcccc43204b"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-books-to-read-which-can-improve-my-soft-skills?-", 
    "answer" : "Kenzie FinleyAnswered 1 year agoWhat are some good books to read which can improve my soft skills? Kenzie Finley Soft Skills: The software developer's life manual 1st Edition  Summary Soft Skills: The software developer's life manual is a unique guide, offering techniques and practices for a more satisfying life as a professional software developer. In it, developer and life coach John Sonmez addresses a wide range of important \"soft\" topics, from career and productivity to personal finance and investing, and even fitness and relationships, all from a developer-centric viewpoint. Forewords by Robert C. Martin (Uncle Bob) and Scott Hanselman. Purchase of the print book includes a free eBook in PDF, Kindle, and ePub formats from Manning Publications. About the Book For most software developers, coding is the fun part. The hard bits are dealing with clients, peers, and managers, staying productive, achieving f Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:14:43.139+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are some good books to read which can improve my soft skills? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e221eed0dadcccc43205c"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-soft-skills-a-spy-should-have?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some soft skills a spy should have?", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:15:26.300+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are some soft skills a spy should have? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602e2232ed0dadcccc432071"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-soft-skills?-Can-I-improve-them-by-reading-books?-", 
    "answer" : "It might be your hard skills that get you the interview, but it’s the soft skills that bring you success in your career. Soft skills are your personal capabilities that determine how well you work with others, job performance, communication and all of the other things that make you different from every other expert in your field. While your technical expertise is very important, soft skills are much harder to teach. These can be a deciding factor in getting and keeping your dream job. In this post, we’ll outline nine soft skills that will make you successful in your career or in the classroom, and some tips to help you develop them further. Interpersonal communication is the backbone of all soft skills. Whether it’s through emails, phone calls or in person, you need to be a clear communicat Continue Reading It might be your hard skills that get you the interview, but it’s the soft skills that bring you success in your career. Soft skills are your personal capabilities that determine how well you work with others, job performance, communication and all of the other things that make you different from every other expert in your field. While your technical expertise is very important, soft skills are much harder to teach. These can be a deciding factor in getting and keeping your dream job. In this post, we’ll outline nine soft skills that will make you successful in your career or in the classroom, and some tips to help you develop them further. Interpersonal communication is the backbone of all soft skills. Whether it’s through emails, phone calls or in person, you need to be a clear communicat Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-18T08:15:46.277+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the most important soft skills to have? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
